<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<config:glue-configuration xmlns:config="urn:X-quest.com:glue/config/1.6" xmlns:ns2="urn:X-quest.com:glue/config/1.5" xmlns:ns3="urn:X-quest.com:glue/config/1.4" xmlns:ns4="urn:X-quest.com:glue/config/1.3" xmlns:ns5="urn:X-quest.com:glue/config/1.2" xmlns:ns6="urn:X-quest.com:glue/config/1.1" xmlns:ns7="urn:X-quest.com:glue/config/1.0">
    <config:host-id>
        <config:documentation>
            This required setting provides a unique identifier for this FglAM
            instance. It is generated during the installation of FglAM and
            should not normally be changed.

            Using an arbitrary UUID instead of this machine's host name allows:
            - Multiple instances to run on one machine simultaneously
            - This machine can be uniquely identified even if the host name is
              changed

            If this value is commented out FglAM will replace it with a randomly
            generated ID and re-read the file.
        </config:documentation>
        <config:id>a0ae8491-e739-4e3f-a196-545e3e51528c</config:id>
    </config:host-id>
    <config:host-display-name>
        <config:documentation>
            Set the host name reported by this FglAM instance. This name will be
            used for all metrics recorded by a this instance of the Foglight Agent
            Monitor.

            If it is not provided it will be automatically detected. If a
            machine is configured with multiple IP addresses or hostnames,
            there is no way to know which will be automatically selected.
            Setting the hostname property specifically in the case is
            recommended.
        </config:documentation>
        <config:name>pc-tshy (C:\Users\TSHY\ws\fglam-devkit-5_6_10-windows-x86_64\state)</config:name>
        <config:warn-on-difference>true</config:warn-on-difference>
    </config:host-display-name>
    <config:secure-launcher>
        <config:documentation>
            A few agents require more permissions that FglAM is ideally granted
            to perform their instrumentation.  In those few cases a separate
            application (usually configured during installation) can be used to
            selectively grant the required permission to those agents.
        </config:documentation>
        <config:path></config:path>
    </config:secure-launcher>
    <config:http-upstreams>
        <config:documentation>
            HTTP upstream connection information is specified using a list of
            http-upstream elements.  Each element contains the following
            attributes:

            Required:
            ---------
               url         URL of the upstream host or FglAM concentrator

            Optional:
            ---------
               address     Address specifies a local network interface
                           that will be used for upstream connections.
                           If it is not provided then the OS is free
                           to decide which local interface to use.

               proxy       URL of the proxy server to use when connecting to
                           the specified URL.

               proxy-user  Username to use when authenticating with the proxy
                           server.

               proxy-pass  Password to use then authentication with the proxy
                           server. Passwords will be encrypted and written back
                           to this file. To change a password, simply replace the
                           encrypted value with the new, unencrypted, password and 
                           restart FglAM.

               proxy-ntlm-domain Windows domain to use for NTLM proxy authentication.
                           If your Windows user name is 'WORKGROUP\\user' then you
                           would set proxy-user to 'user' and proxy-ntlm-domain to
                           'WORKGROUP'. The proxy-user cannot also contain the
                           Windows domain.

               ssl-allow-self-signed 'true' if self-signed SSL certificates
                           will be accepted and 'false' if they are not. The
                           default, if not specified, is 'false'. When set, only
                           the host name of the server's SSL certificate is
                           checked, the certificate chain and signer are *not*
                           checked. 'self-signed' in this case refers to an
                           SSL certificate signed by an unknown Certificate
                           Authority. i.e., one that you signed youself.

               ssl-cert-common-name 'hostname' If provided, the SSL certificate
                           from the server will be validate against this host
                           name, rather than the name of the server FglAM
                           connected to. This can be used when the certificate
                           on the server does not match the host name of the
                           server as viewed from the client.  You should not
                           normally have to set this field.

                compressed 'true' if GZIP compression should be used for server
                           communications.  This can often reduce the amount of
                           bandwidth required, at the cost of higher CPU and
                           memory usage.  The default, if not specified, is true.

            FglAM will attempt to connect to the first http-upstream in the
            list. If that fails then FglAM will iterate through the list from
            the beginning and try to find a connection.

            Installing New Root Certificates
            --------------------------------

            If a SSL certificate signed by a private Certificate Authority (CA) is used, 
            and must be checked for a valid signer, then a new Certificate Authority 
            must be added to the Agent Manager. The Agent Manager command line options

              --list-certificates
              --add-certificate
              --delete-certificate

            can be used to add and remove CA certificates while the Agent Manager is 
            running.

            **NOTE:** The certificate file to be imported should be the public certificate
            for the Certificate Authority that signed the server's SSL certificate, not the
            SSL certificate itself. Also, once you have imported the Certificate Authority,
            you should set 'ssl-allow-self-signed' to false as the certificate from the server
            is no longer considered signed by a private certificate authority.

			An example child element of the http-upstreams parent node might be:

			http-upstream url="http://localhost:8080"
                       address="127.0.0.1"
                       proxy="http://proxy.example.com:9000"
                       proxy-user="username"
                       proxy-ntlm-domain="WORKGROUP"
                       proxy-pass="password"
                       ssl-allow-self-signed="true"
                       ssl-cert-common-name="server-name-as-seen-by-client"
                       
            Excluding Specific SSL Ciphers
            ------------------------------
            
            If you need to exclude one or more ciphers from the SSL encryption used
            for SSL connections, you can do so using one or more excluded-ssl-cipher
            elements. Common reasons for this include excluding lower encryption strength
            ciphers, or excluding ciphers with security vulnerabilities until they can
            be patched.
            
            For example:
            
            http-upstream url="https://some.secure.system:8443"
               excluded-ssl-cipher name="SSL_RSA_WITH_RC4_128_MD5"
               excluded-ssl-cipher name="SSL_RSA_EXPORT_WITH_DES40_CBC_SHA"
               excluded-ssl-cipher name="SSL_DHE_DSS_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA"

		</config:documentation>
        <config:http-upstream url="http://localhost:8080"/>
    </config:http-upstreams>
    <config:http-downstreams>
        <config:documentation>
            HTTP downstream connection information specified the addresses that
            this FglAM instance will listen on for downstream FglAM clients.
            This allows FglAM instances to act as concentrators.

            The addresses specify a 'port' that will accept incoming FglAM
            connections and an optional 'address' that will specify which
            network interface will be listened to.

            Most FglAM clients do not need this setting.

			Example child elements of the http-downstreams parent node includes:

			http-downstream port="9090"

			or

			http-downstream port="9090" address="127.0.0.1"

            FglAM also supports configuring HTTPS/SSL downstream connections by
            configuring one or more https-downstream elements.  These support
            the port and address attributes from the http-downstream element
            as well the following additional attributes:

            Required:
            ---------
               key-password The password required to access the private key
                           contained in the keystore. This will be automatically
                           encrypted if needed.

            Optional:
            ---------
               keystore    Path to the file containing the keystore to use.  If
                           this is a relative path it will be resolved from
                           this FglAM instance's state directory.

               keystore-password The password for the keystore itself.  This is
                           typically the same as the value of key-password and
                           only needs to be specified if the passwords differ.
                           This will be automatically encrypted if needed.

               ssl-key-manager-factory-algorithm The algorithm used by the
                           keystore to manage keys.  This does not normally
                           need to be set.

               truststore  Path to the file containing the set of trusted
                           certificates.  These are the certificates that are
                           checked when downstream clients provide their own
                           certificates during authentication.

                           If this is a relative path it will be resolved from
                           this FglAM instance's state directory.

               truststore-type The type of truststore.  This does not normally
                           need to be explicitly set.

               truststore-password The password used to access the truststore.
                           This will be automatically encrypted if needed.

               ssl-trust-manager-factory-algorithm The algorithm used by the
                           truststore to manage keys.  This does not normally
                           need to be set.

               need-client-auth 'true' if downstream clients connecting to this
                           FglAM instance are required to authenticate
                           themselves, 'false' otherwise.  If not specified the
                           default is 'false'.

               want-client-auth 'true' if the server should request that
                           downstream clients authenticate themselves.  Unlike
                           need-client-auth, if the downstream client does not
                           authenticate itself it will still be allowed to
                           connect to this FglAM instance.  If not specified
                           the default is 'false'.

               algorithm   The encryption algorithm used to generate keys in
                           the keystore.  This does not normally need to be
                           set.

               protocol    Secure protocol supported, either SSL or TLS.  This
                           does not normally need to be set.

               provider    The cryptographic algorithm provider.  This does not
                           normally need to be set.

               secure-random-algorithm The name of the random number generation
                           algorithm to use.  This does not normally need to be
                           set.
                           
           Password Security:
           ------------------
               The passwords required for the key-password, keystore-password, and 
               truststore-password will be encrypted automatically when this file is
               read by FglAM. The encrypted versions will then be written over top of
               the unencrypted version.
               
               If you need to change any of these passwords, you can simply replace the
               encrypted password with the new, unencrypted value and restart FglAM.
               
           Excluding Specific SSL Ciphers
           ------------------------------
            
               If you need to exclude one or more ciphers from the SSL encryption used
               for SSL connections, you can do so using one or more excluded-ssl-cipher
               elements. Common reasons for this include excluding lower encryption strength
               ciphers, or excluding ciphers with security vulnerabilities until they can
               be patched.
            
               For example:
            
               https-downstream port="8443"
                   excluded-ssl-cipher name="SSL_RSA_WITH_RC4_128_MD5"
                   excluded-ssl-cipher name="SSL_RSA_EXPORT_WITH_DES40_CBC_SHA"
                   excluded-ssl-cipher name="SSL_DHE_DSS_WITH_3DES_EDE_CBC_SHA"                   
        </config:documentation>
    </config:http-downstreams>
    <config:polling>
        <config:documentation>
            These settings control how often this installation will instruct
            downstream hosts and agents to connect and poll for messages. The
            more hosts that are connected, the less often they will be
            instructed to poll.

            Changing these settings is only recommended when instructed to do
            so by Quest support.  Most FglAM clients do not need to change these
            settings.

            The polling rate is controlled by the following elements:

               min-polling-interval The minimum polling interval, in seconds.

               max-polls-per-minute The maximum number of polls per minute. Client
                           polling intervals will be adjusted to adhere to this.

               max-delay-factor The multiplier for the maximum delay, based on
                           the computed minimum delay.

               upstream-offset The offset used for upstream polling. The client is
                           given a min. and max. value for when to connect to the
                           upstream server. If there are upstream messages pending,
                           we always connect at the minimum time. If there are no
                           messages pending, then we connect at the max interval
                           minus this offset. The offset should be large enough that
                           the client does not miss the max. polling interval because
                           of a slow connection.
               min-polling-timeout A fudge factor (in seconds) that will be added to
                           the time we wait before a host is considered disconnected.
                           This is used to account for clock skews and changes in
                           timing typically seen on heavily loaded VMWare images.

        </config:documentation>
        <config:min-polling-interval>5</config:min-polling-interval>
        <config:max-polls-per-minute>500</config:max-polls-per-minute>
        <config:max-delay-factor>3.5</config:max-delay-factor>
        <config:upstream-offset>10.0</config:upstream-offset>
        <config:min-polling-timeout>60</config:min-polling-timeout>
    </config:polling>
    <config:queue-sizes>
        <config:documentation>
            FglAM accumulates messages that are destined to be sent either upstream or
            downstream in queues between connections.  This prevents messages from
            getting lost in the event of a disconnection.

            The 'MaxQueueSize' setting specifies the maximum number of messages that
            will be stored in the queue.  If the queue overflows then the newest messages
            will be discarded.  Zero  means no messages will be queued, -1 means that the
            queues will be allowed to grow indefinitely.

            'MaxDiskSpace' indicates how much disk space (in kB) can be used to store
            messages.  If zero then messages will never be written to disk, -1 means no
            limit.

            'MaxBatchSize' is the number of messages that will be sent from the queue when
            a connection has successfully been made.  -1 means every available message will
            be included in each batch.

            Changing these settings is only recommended when instructed to do so by Quest
            support.  Most FglAM clients will use the default settings.
            
            The upstream verified queue includes additional restrictions on the values.
            In particular, the 'MaxQueueSize' can never be 0, and the 'MaxDiskSpace' can
            never be 0. 
        </config:documentation>
        <config:upstream max-queue-size="-1" max-disk-space="1024" max-batch-size="500" allow-runtime-change="true"/>
        <config:upstream-verified max-queue-size="-1" max-disk-space="512" max-batch-size="250" allow-runtime-change="true"/>
        <config:downstream max-queue-size="-1" max-disk-space="1024" max-batch-size="500" allow-runtime-change="true"/>
    </config:queue-sizes>
    <config:time-sync max-allowed-variation="300000">
        <config:documentation>
    		The maximum allowed variation (in ms) in the time sync (difference between the 
    		system time and the upstream time) before previous values are discarded and 
    		the time synchronization is reset. This defaults to 5 minutes. If a time 
    		difference that is more than 5 minutes different from the previous value 
    		is recorded, then we assume the upstream clock has been change and we 
    		restart the client's time synchronization.
    	</config:documentation>
    </config:time-sync>
    <config:jfogbank>
        <config:documentation>
            Sets some default values that the JFogbank server use when it begins accepting con
            connections from legacy Fog4 agents.  The default values should be kept in most
            cases, but the occasional exceptional system might need timeouts increased if it
            runs much more slowly or a fixed port is desired.

            Changing these settings is only recommended when instructed to do so by Quest
            support.  Most FglAM clients will use the default settings.
        </config:documentation>
        <config:port>0</config:port>
        <config:loginTimeout>30000</config:loginTimeout>
        <config:bridgeTimeout>120000</config:bridgeTimeout>
    </config:jfogbank>
    <config:kerberos>
        <config:documentation>
			Configures the location of the configuration files used by Kerberos to locate
			the Key Distribution Center (KDC) and perform login.  If the krb5-config
			element is missing or empty then FglAM will search for a suitable file on the
			host filesystem.  The following locations will be searched, in order:
			- %WINDIR%/krb5.ini
			- /etc/krb5.conf
			- /etc/krb5/krb5.conf

			If a file cannot be located then FglAM will attempt to generate one using
			guessed values and will store it in the config directory.  This element will
			be updated.

			Relative paths are resolved according to FglAM's state directory.

			This value can be overridden at runtime using the following command line switch:
			-Djava.security.krb5.conf=/path/to/file
		</config:documentation>
        <config:krb5-config-file></config:krb5-config-file>
        <config:login-config-file></config:login-config-file>
        <config:subject-creds-only>false</config:subject-creds-only>
        <config:debug>false</config:debug>
    </config:kerberos>
</config:glue-configuration>
